{
    "id": "80662e677ac2435785aa29e552ba9f52",
    "title": "Spelling And Vocabulary Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "57a9991cc6764b589c1325878c7215ab",
            "title": "Spelling And Vocabulary Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The army’s disorganized retreat was ………………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ignominous",
                        "ignominious",
                        "ignominius"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Individualists cannot accept community ……………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "idology",
                        "ideology",
                        "ideologi"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………….. of the law is no excuse.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Ignorance",
                        "Ignoranse",
                        "Ignorrance"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Spring makes everyone feel ……………………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "idol",
                        "idle",
                        "idlle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The senator showed his ………………………………. by saying he was for the bill and then voting against it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hypocrisy",
                        "hipocricy",
                        "hyppocricy"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The medical students were asked how they would treat a ………………………….. illness.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hipothetical",
                        "hypothetical",
                        "hypotheticcal"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Both parents grew ……………………………… when they couldn’t find the child.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hysterical",
                        "histerical",
                        "hysterycal"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is the ……………………………. among us who try to aid humanity.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "idolists",
                        "idealists",
                        "ideolists"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The doctor gave an …………………………. of the dangers of poor nutrition.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "illustration",
                        "ilustration",
                        "illustrasion"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The artist’s …………………………… use of color delighted the critics.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "imaginative",
                        "imaginetive",
                        "immaginative"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was an …………………………. actor.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ilustrious",
                        "illustrious",
                        "illustrous"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The fabric isn’t real silk, only an ……………………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "immitation",
                        "imtation",
                        "imitation"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}